planetmirror.com 2002-08-02

# Planet Mirror privacy

Planet Mirror Privacy Policy  
Planet Mirror is committed to ensuring the privacy of your information. We understand how important the privacy of your personal information is to you and have in place robust policies, procedures, software and hardware that will ensure your information and transaction details are at all times secure and your privacy is protected. 

Visitor Information  
Our web server collects anonymous statistical data for information purposes from visitors to our website, such as traffic patterns, pages viewed, date and time, number of visitors, etc. No attempt is made to identify these visitors. 

Information You Supply  
Planet Mirror requires you to provide certain information in order to register with us such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We will not use your personal information for any purpose which is not related to the provision of services by Planet Mirror. 

Where required by law, we may release information however, we will not sell or disclose your information to any individual or entity outside Planet Mirror without your permission. 

Email  
Your e-mail address may be used to notify you of improvements or other changes to Planet Mirror or for newsletters, updates and special offers. If we send you an email for information or promotional purposes, you will always be given the option of not receiving any further emails of this kind. 

Transmitted Data Security  
When you transmit data to Planet Mirror it is passed through a secure server.  
In addition, all stored customer information is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure passwords and other security procedures. 
Planet Mirror Privacy Policy  
Planet Mirror is committed to ensuring the privacy of your information. We understand how important the privacy of your personal information is to you and have in place robust policies, procedures, software and hardware that will ensure your information and transaction details are at all times secure and your privacy is protected. 

Visitor Information  
Our web server collects anonymous statistical data for information purposes from visitors to our website, such as traffic patterns, pages viewed, date and time, number of visitors, etc. No attempt is made to identify these visitors. 

Information You Supply  
Planet Mirror requires you to provide certain information in order to register with us such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We will not use your personal information for any purpose which is not related to the provision of services by Planet Mirror. 

Where required by law, we may release information however, we will not sell or disclose your information to any individual or entity outside Planet Mirror without your permission. 

Email  
Your e-mail address may be used to notify you of improvements or other changes to Planet Mirror or for newsletters, updates and special offers. If we send you an email for information or promotional purposes, you will always be given the option of not receiving any further emails of this kind. 

Transmitted Data Security  
When you transmit data to Planet Mirror it is passed through a secure server.  
In addition, all stored customer information is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure passwords and other security procedures.
